that I will use.
I need a high -resolution image to make
a credible, create a credible window and it has discovered
That GoPro cameras work great.
But the modern ones are not suitable so I get back down in age
And I bought a used on the block.
GoPro 7 Black is exactly the model I need
Because it is the only thing I manage to find that has HDMI exit.
It is also used as webcams, high quality webcams
GoPro 7 will be my eye out into the world.
And so I have OLED TV, 4K OLED TV to create a picture.
We can look at it.
I have an elevated floor partly.
Biggest reason is that I wanted a huge storage space
Below the double floor is 25 centimeters high and very spacious,
So I have two half a meter long and 25 centimeters high and one meter wide.
Stuff that I don't use as often or that is very bulky
is perfect to be able to store.
The perfect opportunity to collect things.
I will have more space than I need when I'm done.
A pleasant problem to have in a camper.
Winter clothes in summer and summer clothes in winter.
And a snowboard.
If I want to go out and go and there are always things to fill with.
A little bigger things they hide under the bed?
Yes, the bed is the garage.
There you have the biggest stuff, type of electric mop and big bulky things.
Then you have medium -sized things I will have 2 pieces
Under the stomach of the truck between the wheel axles.
There I have partly the battery system and partly I will have hose
And collapsible ladder you need.
So there we also have a lot of storage space.
This is actually something that I have been thinking a great deal
on how I would solve it.
The platform that I fold down is my balcony
And it has been remote controlled.
Via a remote control only, but it must have a winch system
that winch it up and all the winches are watching
Are very nice and great and oversized for this wall.
The platform weighs 180 kilos and then we are in at 4, 5, 6, 7 tons
How can I get hold of a smaller winch?
And then I got a flash.
It is quad bikes to ATV winch so I checked it up